Daniel Peralta de la Herrán.

+34680701472

Email: dani.peralta.de@gmail.com

GitHub: DaniPeralta Skype:danielperalta91

I have a degree in Computer Engineering, and my interest in acquiring training in computer security skills has led me to do a Master in Cybersecurity. With national and international experience in web development, handling large volumes of data and cybersecurity.

Experience

2023-2024 (January - December): Fullstack Developer: Swisslinx.

Freelance for Swiss company on remote. Development of internal applications for recruitment company. Backend development in **PHP** with **Laravel** and frontend with **HTML5**, **CSS3** and **Javascript**. **MySQL** and **SQL Server** DBMS. Maintenance and improvement of an application in **VB ASP Classic**. Use of tools such as **Git**, **Jira**, **IntelliJ**, **Slack**, **Docker**.

2021 - 2023 (December - January): Fullstack Developer: Elims.

Development of the application for internal use of the company's dental clinics. Back-end development in **PHP** with **Laravel**. In addition to small front-end developments with **HTML5** (with Blade templates), **CSS3** and **Javascript**. Development scripts for **SQL Server** and **MySQL**.

2021 (May - October): Team Leader & C++ Developer: Escribano Mechanical & Engineering.

Coordination of a team of three people, all remotely, for the complete developments of a project in its different phases of analysis, design, implementation and test, applying the RUP methodology.

Use of tools such as **Redmine**, **Jenkins**, **Sonarqube**, **Enterprise** as well as **Qt Creator** for development.

2020 - 2021 (December - April): C# Developer: Cádiz City Council.

Development of a module of the Social Services desktop application, with Web Forms in **C#** and **Oracle** database.

2020 (May – December): PHP/Symfony Developer: Antonio de Nebrija University.

Development of a REST API for the integration of external services with **Symfony 5** and **API-Platform**. ETL process improvement and visualization with **Power BI**.

2020 (Enero - April): VB & SQL Server Developer: CT Engineers / Airbus.

Development of a management project, at the **Airbus** plant in Puerto Real, in the **Visual Basic** programming language. Management and improvement of the database in **Microsoft SQL Server**.

2018-2019 (May - November): **Research Staff: University of Cadiz**.

Development in several research projects, from the development of an application with **Unity3D**, development plugins for **Moodle** in **PHP** and development of real time data processing projects with **WSO2 Stream Processing**. Development **Android** app and a **Java** API.

2017-2018 (October - February): PHP Developer and Database Designer: MBet.

PHP web development with the **Symfony3** framework.

Design of a new **database** model for a sports betting company and management of the **ETL** process for data transfer.

2016-2017 (September - October): PHP and T-SQL Developer: Antonio de Nebrija University.

Development of university management applications with PHP5.

Development of ETL processes with **T-SQL** - **Microsoft SQL Server**.

2014-2015 (March - July): BI Process Developer (Pentaho) / Web Development: University of Cadiz.

Internship for the development of applications based on **Business Intelligence** processes using the **Pentaho** tool.

Development and maintenance of an application developed in **Python/Django** and another in **PHP/Symfony**.

2011 (March - June): Development VB .NET: Cápsulas Torrent, S.A.

Internship for the development of computer applications in the programming language Visual Basic .NET.

Education

2018-2019 (October - September): Master in Cybersecurity: University of Cádiz (Spain)

- **2019 (July September)**
 - Master's Degree Project: University of Magdalena (Colombia)
 - Master's Degree Project in Cybersecurity as part of the software development research group at the University of Magdalena, Santa Marta, Colombia.

2011 - 2015: Degree in Computer Engineering. Information Systems Specialization: University of Cádiz (Spain)

- 2016 (January June)
 - Final Project: University San Carlos (Guatemala)
 - Development of a web application in Python with the Django framework for the Mobility department of the Faculty of Engineering.

2009 - 2011: Higher Technical in Development of Computer Applications.

English

December - 2015: Trinity College London - ISE II (B2)

May - 2015: Cambridge English Preliminary - PET (B1).